Sonic was watching his soon-to-be lover
Bartleby Montclair of Dresden where are
they you asked at the New York Yankees
baseball stadium Bartleby is up to bat
next if he gets a homerun this would be
his 230 second home run this game alone
everyone was cheering for him even I
Sonic the Hedgehog couldn't help but
cheer at top of my lungs for the sexy
blonde man to me
Bartleby is someone special even more
special than my own siblings Sonia and
medic Bartleby is someone I would give
up my life for someone I want to protect
someone I want to bang me in the ass
it was then I heard his deep masculine
voice wish me luck
my fat Lubitsch Bartleby said as I
turned around to meet his gaze he gave
me a good hard spanking the butt cheeks
I could feel the sweat from down my neck
going down my back and into my butt
crack what is this feeling could it be
love no it can't be
we only see each other as friends
nothing more and nothing less but I do
have to admit his butt cheeks are like
two big fat plump and juicy watermelons
at the beginning of spring that I want
to squeeze with great force and never
let go like oh my God oh yes my mouth
was drooling at just the thought of his
has but day dreaming of my plump ass
again I see
Bartleby said Oh Oh Bartleby
I I didn't know you were standing there
well I am and since you like it so much
he'll make sure you get a good view of
it Bartleby said as he winked at me
which gave me a nosebleed because he
looked so [ __ ] sexy
next batter up the coach said and with
that it was Barbie's turn he grabbed his
baseball bat put on his cap and walked
out onto the field he got into his ready
stance this was it the moment the entire
crowd was waiting for everyone who came
here came here for one thing alone to
watch Bartleby even those who don't even
like baseball came to see Bartleby
silence filled the air
the pitcher groped the ball and his fist
he threw the ball through the air at
great speed
and then strike one what is this
Bartleby got a strike that can't be
possible
I looked around and people were agreeing
with me and shouting with pure rage is
the ball pitcher cheating Bart levy
never got a strike before in his entire
life and then I heard the words I didn't
want to hear strike two
no stop it I said but the pitcher just
laughed at me as I pulled out my
telescope to get a better view Bartleby
was crying why and then it hit me if
Bart levy wins this game he will get an
invitation to the major leagues he will
leave country but more importantly he
will leave me as doing this for me
Bartleby I said as I stood up from my
seat you can do this Bartleby even if we
are far apart remember we will always be
in each other hearts because you are my
friend no you are my lover I could feels
tears falling from my eyes Bartleby
smiled and looked up at me well if it
isn't my Beach the one with the book
cheeks that looked like to plump
grapefruits the whole crowd started to
cheer as Bartleby winked at me he walked
over to the crowd and started to sign
autographs he even gave a sweet little
boy a lollipop Wow Bartleby is so kind
now if you all excuse me I have a game
to finish Bartleby said walking back to
the batters area what's this he doesn't
have a baseball bat the whole stadium
was confused but I wasn't
I knew Bart levy wouldn't need it
because he's Bart levy the pitcher threw
the ball as fast as he could and just
then Bartleby reached out his hand and
caught the ball the ground was now
giving a thunderous applause here you go
you can have this back Bartleby said as
he threw the baseball back at the
pitcher
the pitcher turned to run but it was
already too late the baseball went right
up his ass he fell to the floor
screaming in pain the people were
cheering from the stents homerun the
coach said no no everyone I don't
deserve all the credit after all I
couldn't have done it without my Beach I
blushed
just then Bartleby ripped off his
clothes
everyone was cheering as Bartleby jumped
on top of me and started to bang me in
the ass
Bartleby I love you I know baby I know